Anton Zaharia

London, CR7 8LW | willing to relocate | +44 736 711 1009 | zahariaanton95@gmail.com Github | Blog | Homepage | Linkedin

JOB TITLE

Experienced in Ruby on Rails and JavaScript-based programming and a background in multi-drop delivery services, on-site surveying, and restaurant management. Possess strong communication, decision-making, and problem-solving skills to deliver great customer service, as well as excellent organizing and planning skills that enable adaptability and help to provide the first-class service and meet deadlines.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Ruby, Rails, SQL, Javascript, React, Redux, Sinatra, Bootstrap, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), HTML

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Raffle - Github | Demo

Raffle is a web app that provides several contests where any user can buy tickets and participate.

- Utilized the built-in React toolkit to build user-facing features.
- Building React components to boost productivity and to facilitate further maintenance.
- Utilized Redux data-flow architecture to organize the app state.
- Implemented Thunk Middleware to ensure an asynchronous movement of the app.

Topz - SPA - Github | Demo

Topz is a one-page app that shows a list of user-created tops, about any topic. Any user can create, add a new option, and vote for any top.

- Developed a Rails API backend with endpoints for tops, options, and votes.
- Handling user events and changing DOM elements to deliver an interactive user interface.
- Used asynchronous techniques to ensure a continuously working app for the user.

RGadgets - Github | Demo

RGadgets it's a web app created in Ruby on Rails that simulates a website for an online store.

- Utilized B-Crypt Gem to ensure a safe storing of users passwords.
- Designed the app using the MVC pattern to implement the separation of concepts.
- Made use of OAuth Gem to implement a safe and fast login/signup for the user.
- Used the Bootstrap framework to create a modern website front-end.

More projects can be seen on antonzaharia.com

EXPERIENCE

Now-u Ruby on Rails Developer - Volunteer London, UK

Dec 2020 - Present

- Working independently to complete agile tasks which include writing clean, maintainable and efficient code.
- Designing robust, scalable and secure features and contributing in all phases of the development lifecycle.

Integrity Software Limited

London, UK Oct 2020 - Present

Full Stack Web Developer - Contractor

- Working independently to build a fully functional website frontend in React, from a mock example.
- Communicating with the design team to complete tasks and upgrading the website features.
- Integrating Ruby on Rails backend for the React frontend to facilitate further development.

Hermes, Amazon, BCCP

London, UK

Sept 2017 - Present

Multi-drop delivery driver
Created a program, and planned every 2 minutes of the shift to set an estimated time of arrival.

- Created a program, and planned every 2 minutes of the shift to set an estimated time of arrival.
 Resulted in 97.5 % completion of deliveries, collections, and ETA daily.
- Adhering to assigned routes and following time schedules resulted in 100% routes completion.
- Communicating directly with the customers to ensure an exceptional experience, respecting customer instructions, helped me to maintain a 95% positive customer satisfaction rating.

- Abiding by all transportation laws and adapting to any road situations helped me to maintain a clean driving record with 0 penalty points over 3 years.
- Involving in extra hours of work to help to complete daily assignments, resulting in above 90% of monthly responsibilities completed.

Vype On-site surveyor London, UK Sept 2016 - Sept 2017

- Travelling to circa 570 WHSmith UK stores, meeting all deadlines and performance requirements by 100%.
- Communicating and working with 2-3 members of 5 different teams daily, resulting in a 5-star performance rating.

Papa Johns Store Manager London, UK

Sept 2014 - Sept 2016

- Respond to customer complaints and concerns in a professional manner to achieve 12% sale growth.
- Delivered excellent customer satisfaction achieving top-performing franchise in London.
- Ensure store compliance with health and safety regulations to achieve 100 points on the Mistery Shopper checks.

EDUCATION

Flatiron School

London, UK

Full Stack Web Development, Ruby on Rails and JavaScript program

Jan 2020 - Oct 2020

Udemy

Online, 2020

Certified Web Developer, Javascript Beginner to Pro Certificate

Zenva Academy

Online, 2018

<u>JavaScript Programming - Learn by Creating a Cross-Platform Game</u> <u>Learn HTML and CSS by Creating a Responsive Company Website</u>

Theoretic College 'Mircea Eliade'

Galati, Romania

Baccalaureate Diploma, Diploma in Social Science

2014